A Guide to the Retired Faculty Association Papers, 1983-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Retired Faculty Association Papers RG-24/31/1.991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-24/31/1.991
This collection consists of 500 (ca.) items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1999 August 10.
Scope and Content Information
Papers contain agendas, correspondence, financial records, memberships lists, minutes, newsletters, and miscellaneous items.
Topics include biographies of guest speakers, the University of Virginia Capital Campaign, the "Change and Improvement in Virginia Higher Education" report of the State Council for Higher Education in Virginia; the Virginia Academy of Learning proposal
Contents List
- Biographies of Speakers 1992-1994 (Box 1)
- Capital Campaign for the University of Virginia 1992-1993 (Box 1)
- Change and Improvement Report for State Council on Higher Education 1993 (Box 1)
- Correspondence (4 folders) 1991-1997 (Box 1)
- Luncheons and Events Finances 1990-1997 (Box 1)
- Membership Rosters 1988-1997 (Box 1)
- Minutes 1991-1997 (Box 2)
- Models for Institutes for Learning in Retirement 1983, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
- Models for Retirement Associations 1990-1995 (Box 2)
- Newsletter 1993 Mar-Apr (Box 2)